A Guide to the WRVA Radio Collection, 1925-2000
Library of Virginia
- Series XIII: News Tape Morgue, 1 January 1980-31 December 1999., Extent: 15 boxes. (Box 72-86)
  This series contains WRVA local and statewide news reports from 1 January 1980-31 December 1999. Available in digital format upon request. A printed multi-volume chronological inventory by year is available for use in the Library.
  Chronological
  - 1 January 1980-22 October 1980., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 72)
  - 22 October 1980-19 August 1981., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 73)
  - 19 August 1981-7 September 1982., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 74)
  - 8 September 1982-31 December 1983., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 75)
  - 2 January 1984-20 May 1985., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 76)
  - 21 May 1985-2 July 1986., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 77)
  - 3 July 1986-28 August 1987., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 78)
  - 31 August 1987-13 February 1989., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 79)
  - 13 February 1989-2 October 1990., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 80)
  - 2 October 1990-23 April 1992., 42 cassette tapes. (Box 81)
  - 24 April 1992-28 October 1993., 40 cassette tapes. (Box 82)
  - 28 October 1993-17 July 1995., 35 cassette tapes. (Box 83)
  - 17 July 1995-31 December 1996., 33 cassette tapes. (Box 84)
  - 2 January 1997-21 September 1998., 41 cassette tapes. (Box 85)
  - 21 September 1998-31 December 1999., 28 cassette tapes. (Box 86)
- Series XIV: Special Programs and Airchecks, 1 January 1981-31 December 1994., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 87-96)
  This series contains snippets of Virginia news reported by WRVA from 1 January 1981 - 31 December 1999. Highlights include election coverage and political activities in the state as well as significant local and statewide events such as floods, snowstorms, hurricanes, fires, major traffic accidents, among others. Also includes occasional in-depth looks at significant newsworthy events and anniversary programs and miscellaneous recordings including AP Award entries, and tribute programs. Series is available in digital format upon request. A printed single-volume chronological inventory to the series is available for use in the Library.
  - 1981-1982., 35 cassette tapes. (Box 87)
  - 1983-1984., 40 cassette tapes. (Box 88)
  - 1984-1987., 40 cassette tapes. (Box 89)
  - 1988-1989., 41 cassette tapes. (Box 90)
  - 1989., 38 cassette tapes. (Box 91)
  - 1990., 34 cassette tapes. (Box 92)
  - 1990-1992., 34 cassette tapes. (Box 93)
  - 1992-1993., 34 cassette tapes. (Box 94)
  - 1993-1994., 24 cassette tapes and 3 Digital Audio Tapes. (Box 95)
  - 1985-1993., 15 cassette tapes, 4 reel-to-reel tapes. (Box 96)